在 Apple，设计始终与伟大的想法有关
At apple, design has always been about great ideas.
这些想法的开发过程则又充满了对细节的狂热专注
Those ideas then are developed with this obsessive dedication to detail.
如果我们对组成产品的各种细节足够关注
If we care enough about all the details that make up a product,
那么最后我们设计出的这种体验将使我们感觉到
then in the end we will have designed an experience
不可能有另外的方式能够实现
that really feels like there's no other way it could be.
最好的例子就是 macOS Big Sur
And the best example of this is MacOS Big Sur.
我们的目标是使软件的设计更加清晰
Our goal was to bring even more clarity to the design of the software.
同时保持 Mac 的强大功能和易用性
While retaining the Mac's, powerful capability and ease of use.
我们从最简单的元素开始
We started with the simplest of elements,
从圆角的半径，到按钮和控件的改良
from the shape of a corner radius to refinements in buttons and controls.
我们把符号的统一语言引入了 Mac
And we brought our unified language of symbols to the Mac,
使它们更统一和易于识别
making them more consistent and easier to recognize.
使用深度、阴影和半透明
Depth, shading and translucency
来创建层级
are used to create hierarchy.
这些新材料非常丰富且充满生机
These new materials are rich and they're vibrant.
它们连接着明亮与黑暗
They bridge light and dark.
我们降低了视觉复杂性，以保持对用户内容的关注
We've reduced visual complexity to keep the focus on user's content.
当你需要按钮和控件时，它们会出现
Buttons and controls appear when you need them,
当你不需要时便会隐藏
and they recede when you don't.
访问系统级控件也有着全新的方式
There's a new way to access system-level controls
通知和小组件也有着统一的空间
and a unified space for notifications and widgets.
我们还创建了一套新的声音。
We've also created a new suite of sounds.
都是 Mac 上熟悉的声音，但经过重制，使其更加动听
They're familiar to the Mac, but remastered, and more refined.
我们想让整个生态系统具有一致性
We wanted consistency throughout the ecosystem.
这样，用户就可以在 Apple 设备之间自由切换
The users can move fluidly between the Apple devices.
但我们也喜欢 Mac 的图标，有着深厚的历史印记
But we also love that Mac icons have a deep history
以及独特的外观和感觉
and a distinct look and feel.
所以我们保留了许多精巧的细节
So we've retained many of the highly crafted details
以及使 Mac 图标独一无二的有趣元素
and the playful elements that make Mac icons unique.
这个操作系统反映了重要的历史
This OS reflects an important history.
它让人感觉熟悉，但每一个细节又是全新的
It's familiar, but it's also entirely new in every detail.
我们喜爱 Mac
We love the Mac.
它是我们的工具，用来创造走向世界的产品
It's the tool we use to make all the products that we put out into the world.
macOS Big Sir 是个新的开始
And macOS Big Sir is where it starts.